searchenginenews.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy · SearchEngineNews.com

We know you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will handle everything carefully and responsibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting SearchEngineBook.com, seoINsites.com, SearchEngineNews.com and the rest of Planet Ocean Communications Inc's websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

**Topics Covered in this Notice**

**What Personal Information Does Planet Ocean Gather?**

The information we gather helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at all of Planet Ocean's domains. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on one of our Web sites or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to utilize some of the features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing your transactions with us, improving our sites, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use _cookies_, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our membership sites. 

**What About Cookies?**

  * Cookies are identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized features.
  * The _Help_ portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Planet Ocean membership sites' coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Does Planet Ocean Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. However there may be instances where we are required by law or other mandate to share information in such cases as: 

  * **Protection of Planet Ocean and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Planet Ocean, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**What About Information Security?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?**

SearchEngineNews.com may include third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. 

These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection. 

**Which Information Can I Access?**

If you choose to enroll as a member to any of our sites, you will be provided the means to view and change any personal information stored with us. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information although doing so might prevent you from becoming a member, completing a transaction, or utilizing a feature or function of Planet Ocean's membership sites. 
  * If you become a member of _SearchEngineNews.com_ or _seoINsites.com_ , you can add or update certain information on your personalized page within our Membership Center. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 
  * The _Help_ portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

**Examples of Information Collected**

**Information You Give Us**

You provide us with your information mostly when you make a purchase or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you place an order through SearchEngineBook.com. You provide information in _Your Customer Profile_ \- and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us - whenever you communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise, and whenever you login using your e-mail address and password. 

**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform. The full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

**Information You Can Access**

All enrolled members of _SearchEngineNews.com_ or _seoINsites.com_ , you can easily access up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, phone number) and payment settings on their own personal accounts. 

**Any Further Questions on Privacy Issues can be directed to:Customer Service**
